A Guide to the Memorial Foundation for Children Records, 1811-2006 (bulk 1926-1999)
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Grant files, 1993-2001, 8.3 cu. ft. (24 boxes); Boxes 1-21
  - 1994, IVNA Home Health Care (Box 4, Folder 20a)
  - 1994, Leary Educational Foundation, Timber Ridge School (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 1994, Mary Munford Elementary School (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 1994, Mathematics and Science Center (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1994, Maymont (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1994, Mental Health Association of Virginia (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1994, Minority Youth Appreciation Society (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1994, North Richmond Family YMCA (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1994, Peter Paul Development Center (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1994, Prison Visitation Program (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1994, Rainbow Games (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1994, Refugee and Immigration Services of the Catholic Diocese of Richmond (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1994, Richmond Community High School Advisory Board (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1994, Richmond Public Schools, Thirteen Acres School (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1994, Richmond Symphony (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1994, Richmond Theatre Company for Children of Virginia (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1994, Riverside School (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1994, Sacred Heart Center (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1994, St. James's Children's Center (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1994, St. Joseph's Villa (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 1994, Salvation Army (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 1994, SPARC (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 1994, Stargate (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 1994, Theatre IV (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 1994, Tuckahoe Family YMCA (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 1994, Very Special Arts Virginia (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 1994, VCU School of Arts (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 1994, Virginia Department of Education (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 1994, Virginia Fire and Police Museum (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - 1994, Virginia Foundation for Exceptional Children (Box 5a, Folder 1)
  - 1994, Virginia Home for Boys (Box 5a, Folder 2)
  - 1994, Virginia League for Planned Parenthood (Box 5a, Folder 3)
  - 1994, Virginia Special Olympics (Box 5a, Folder 4)
  - 1994, YMCA of Greater Richmond (Box 5a, Folder 5)
  - 1995, Action Alliance for Virginia's Children and Youth (Box 5a, Folder 6)
  - 1995, Arts Council of Richmond (Box 5a, Folder 7)
  - 1995, Bainbridge and Blackwell Community Development (Box 5b, Folder 1)
  - 1995, Bethlehem Wilson Communities (Box 5b, Folder 2)
  - 1995, Black History Museum (Box 5b, Folder 3)
  - 1995, Boys Inc. (Box 5b, Folder 4)
  - 1995, Camp Holiday Trails (Box 5b, Folder 5)
  - 1995, Carver Promise (Box 5b, Folder 6)
  - 1995, Central Virginia Foodbank (Box 5b, Folder 7)
  - 1995, Challenge Discovery Projects (Box 5b, Folder 8)
  - 1995, Charity Family Life (Box 5b, Folder 9)
  - 1995, Children's Hospital (Box 5b, Folder 10)
  - 1995, Coal Pitt Learning Center (Box 5b, Folder 11)
  - 1995, Cross-Over Ministry (Box 5b, Folder 12)
  - 1995, Easter Seal Society of Virginia (Box 5b, Folder 13)
  - 1995, Elijah House Academy (Box 5b, Folder 14)
  - 1995, Family and Children's Services (Box 5b, Folder 15)
  - 1995, Friends Association for Children (Box 5b, Folder 16)
  - 1995, Garfield Childs Memorial Foundation (Box 5b, Folder 17)
  - 1995, Girls' Club of Richmond (Box 5b, Folder 18)
  - 1995, Goochland County Office on Youth (Box 5b, Folder 19)
  - 1995, Goochland Fellowship and Family Service (Box 5b, Folder 20)
  - 1995, Grace and Holy Trinity Child Care Center (Box 5b, Folder 21)
  - 1995, Thomas H. Henderson Model Middle School (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1995, Jackson-Feild Homes (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1995, John F. Kennedy High School Special Ed Program (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1995, Leary Educational Foundation, Timber Ridge School (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1995, Lewis Ginter Botanical Garden (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1995, Mary Munford Elementary School (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1995, Memorial Child Guidance Clinic (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1995, Minority Youth Appreciation Society (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1995, Museum of the Confederacy (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1995, National Kidney Foundation of Virginia (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1995, New Community School (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1995, Richmond Ballet (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1995, Richmond Children's Museum (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1995, RUPES (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1995, Sacred Heart Center (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1995, St. Jame's Children Center (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1995, St. Joseph's Villa (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1995, Second Presbyterian Child Care Center (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1995, Shenandoah Shakespeare Express (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 1995, Theatre Virginia (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1995, Very Special Arts Virginia (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1995, VMI Foundation (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1995, Virginia Foundation for the Exceptional Child and Adolescent (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1995, Virginia Historical Society (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1995, Virginia Institute of Pastoral Care (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1995, Virginia Museum of Fine Arts Foundation (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1995, Virginia Opera (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1995, Virginia Poverty Law Center (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1995, Virginia State Child Fatality Review Team (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1995, William Byrd Community House (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1995, YMCA of Greater Richmond (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1996, General Requests (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1996, General grant report forms (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1996, American Red Cross (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1996, Andrew's Buddies (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 1996, Arts Council of Richmond (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1996, Black Data Processing Associates (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1996, Black History Museum (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1996, Bon Secours, St. Mary's Health Care Foundation (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1996, Boy Scouts of America, Robert E. Lee Council (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1996, Camp Holiday Trails (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1996, Carver Promise (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1996, Central Virginia Educational Telecommunications Corporation (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1996, Charity Family Life (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1996, Chesapeake Bay Foundation (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1996, Childhood Language Center (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1996, Coal Pitt Learning Center (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1996, Cross-Over Ministry (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1996, Downtown Presents (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1996, Elk Hill Farm (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1996, Family and Children's Service (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1996, Fan Free Clinic (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1996, Goochland Fellowship and Family Service (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1996, Grace and Holy Trinity Child Care Center (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1996, Henricus Foundation (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1996, Hope for the Family Foundation (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1996, IVNA Home Health Care (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 1996, Math and Science Center Foundation (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1996, MCV Arts in the Hospitals (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1996, Memorial Child Guidance Clinic (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1996, Metro Richmond Sports Backers (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 1996, Minority Youth Appreciation Society (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 1996, Richmond Area Association for Retarded Citizens (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 1996, Richmond Public Schools, Mary Munford Elementary School (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 1996, Richmond Public Schools, Real School and Thirteen Acres School (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 1996, Richmond Symphony (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1996, Riverside School (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 1996, Sacred Heart Center (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1996, St. Joseph's Villa (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1996, SCAN, Greater Richmond (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1996, SPARC (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1996, Stargate (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1996, Tourette Syndrome Association (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1996, Very Special Arts Virginia (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1996, Virginia Foundation for the Exceptional Child and Adolescent (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1996, Virginia Heroes (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1996, Virginia Historical Society (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1996, Virginia Home for Boys (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1996, VMI Foundation (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1996, Virginia Special Olympics (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 1996, Volunteer Emergency Families for Children (VEFC) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 1996, William Byrd Community House (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 1996, YMCA of Greater Richmond (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 1997, General applications sent (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1997, Action Alliance for Virginia's Children and Youth (Box 11, Folder 1a)
  - 1997, American Red Cross, Greater Richmond Chapter (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1997, Arts Council of Richmond (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1997, Atlantic Rural Exposition (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1997, Boy Scouts of America, Robert E. Lee Council (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1997, Boys and Girls Club of Richmond (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1997, Boys Home (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1997, Challenge Discovery Project (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1997, Chesapeake Bay Foundation (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1997, Children's Home Society (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1997, Children's Home of Virginia Baptists (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1997, Childhood Language Center at Richmond (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1997, CHIP of Richmond (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 1997, Coal Pitt Learning Center (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 1997, Easter Seal Society of Virginia (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 1997, Elk Hill Farm (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1997, Family and Children's Service (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1997, Friends Association for Children (Box 12, Folder 2a)
  - 1997, Goochland Fellowship and Family Service (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1997, Henrico Court Appointed Special Advocates (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1997, Henricus Foundation (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1997, Hopkins' Road Elementary, Chesterfield County Public Schools (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1997, J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College Educational Foundation (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1997, Jackson-Feild Homes (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1997, Jamestown-Yorktown Educational Trust (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1997, Learning Disabilities Council (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 1997, Leary Educational Foundation (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1997, Lewis Ginter Botanical Garden (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 1997, Math and Science Center Foundation (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 1997, Memorial Child Guidance Clinic (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1997, Minority Youth Appreciation Society (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1997, National Society of the Colonial Dames of America in the Commonwealth of Virginia (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1997, New Community School (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1997, Northstar Academy (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1997, Peter Paul Development Center (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1997, Prevent Blindness Virginia (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 1997, Richmond Ballet (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1997, Richmond Children's Museum (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1997, Richmond Court Appointed Special Advocates (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 1997, Richmond Healthy Start (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 1997, Richmond One to One (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 1997, Richmond Public Schools, Thompson Middle School (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 1997, Sacred Heart Center (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 1997, Science Museum of Virginia Foundation (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 1997, SCRIPT (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1997, 1708 Gallery (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1997, Shenandoah Shakespeare Express (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 1997, Southside Child Development Center (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1997, Stargate (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1997, Thank God for Kids (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 1997, Theatre IV (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 1997, Theatre Virginia (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 1997, United Methodist Family Services (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 1997, Very Special Arts Virginia (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 1997, Virginia Fire and Police Museum (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 1997, Virginia Home for Boys (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 1997, Virginia Institute of Pastoral Care (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 1997, Virginia League for Planned Parenthood (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 1997, Virginia Museum Foundation (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 1997, Virginia Opera (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 1997, Virginia Special Olympics (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1997, YMCA of Greater Richmond (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1998, Action Alliance for Virginia Children and Youth (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1998, American Red Cross (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1998, Arts Council of Richmond (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 1998, Bethlehem Wilson Communities (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 1998, Bon Secours, St. Mary's Health Care Foundation (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 1998, Boys and Girls Club of Richmond (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 1998, Boys Home (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 1998, Camp Holiday Trails (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 1998, Carver Promise (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 1998, Central Virginia's Public Broadcasting (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 1998, Charity Family Life (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1998, Charterhouse School (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1998, Childhood Language Center (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 1998, Children's Hospital (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 1998, Children's Museum of Richmond (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 1998, Coal Pitt Learning Center (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 1998, Commonwealth Girl Scout Council (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 1998, Crestwood Elementary School, Chesterfield County Public Schools (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 1998, Cross-Over Ministry (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 1998, Department Parks and Recreation, City of Richmond (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 1998, Downtown Presents (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 1998, East District Family Resource Center (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 1998, Elijah House Academy (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 1998, Family Advocacy Clinics (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - 1998, Foundation for Exceptional Children (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - 1998, Friends Association for Children (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - 1998, Governor's School for Government and International Studies (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 1998, Grace and Holy Trinity Child Care Center (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 1998, Hanover Tavern Foundation (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 1998, Jewish Community Center of Richmond (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 1998, Junior Achievement (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 1998, Learning Bridge Richmond (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 1998, Leary Educational Foundation (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 1998, Lewis Ginter Botanical Garden (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 1998, Maymont (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 1998, Maymont (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - 1998, Memorial Child Guidance Clinic (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - 1998, National Society of the Colonial Dames of America in the Commonwealth of Virginia (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - 1998, Reading Window School (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 1998, Richmond Public Schools, Broad Rock Elementary School (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 1998, Richmond Public Schools, John Marshall High School (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 1998, Richmond Public Schools, Lucille M. Brown Middle School (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 1998, Richmond Public Schools, Real School and Thirteen Acres School (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 1998, Richmond Symphony (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 1998, Riverside School (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - 1998, Sabot School (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - 1998, Sacred Heart Center (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 1998, St. Andrew's School (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - 1998, St. James's Children's Center (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - 1998, Shenandoah Shakespeare Express (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - 1998, Southeast Chapter of Battens Disease Support and Research Association (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - 1998, Spring Meadow Waldorf School (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - 1998, Theatre IV (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - 1998, United Methodist Family Service (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - 1998, VCU School of Arts (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - 1998, Virginia Holocaust Museum (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - 1998, Virginia Opera (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 1998, William Byrd Community House (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 1998, YMCA of Greater Richmond (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 1999, Art 180 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 1999, Camp Holiday Trails (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 1999, CARITAS (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 1999, Central Virginia Foodbank (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 1999, Central Virginia's Public Television (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 1999, Challenge Discovery Project (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - 1999, Charterhouse School (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - 1999, Chesapeake Bay Foundation (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - 1999, Childhood Language Center (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - 1999, Children's Museum of Richmond (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - 1999, CHIP of Greater Richmond (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 1999, Coal Pitt Learning Center (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - 1999, Crestwood Elementary School (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - 1999, Department Parks and Recreation, City of Richmond (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - 1999, Downtown Presents (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - 1999, Elk Hill Farm (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - 1999, Family and Children's Services (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - 1999, Foundation for Exceptional Children (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - 1999, Friends Association for Children (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - 1999, Garfield Childs Memorial Foundation (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - 1999, George C. Marshall Foundation (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - 1999, Governor's School (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 1999, Grace and Holy Trinity Child Care Center (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 1999, Hand Workshop (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1999, Jamestown-Yorktown Educational Trust (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 1999, Jewish Community Center (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 1999, J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 1999, Learning Bridge Richmond (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 1999, Mathematics and Science Center (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 1999, MCV Arts in the Hospitals (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 1999, Memorial Child Guidance Clinic (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 1999, Minority Youth Appreciation Society (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 1999, New Community School (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - 1999, Northstar Academy (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - 1999, Peter Paul Development Center (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - 1999, Prison Family Support Services (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - 1999, Richmond Boys Choir (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - 1999, Richmond Court Appointed Special Advocates (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - 1999, Richmond Community Action Program (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - 1999, Richmond Goodwill Industries (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1999, Richmond One to One (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 1999, Richmond Reach Out and Read (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 1999, Sacred Heart Center (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 1999, St. Andrew's School (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 1999, Science Museum of Virginia (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 1999, Second Presbyterian Child Care Center (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 1999, Spring Meadow Waldorf School (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 1999, Theatre IV (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 1999, United Methodist Family Services (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 1999, Urban League of Greater Richmond (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 1999, VCU School of Arts (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - 1999, VCU Twin Registry (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - 1999, Very Special Arts Virginia (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - 1999, Virginia Historical Society (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - 1999, Virginia Home for Boys (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - 1999, Virginia Institute of Pastoral Care (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - 1999, Virginia Opera (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - 1999, Virginia Special Olympics (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - 1999, William Byrd Community House (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - 1999, YMCA of Greater Richmond (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - 2001, Virginia Special Olympics (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Series II: Administrative records, 1811-2005 (bulk 1890-1975), 7.9 cu. ft. (22 boxes); Boxes 22-41
  - Account book, 1858-1867 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Account book, 1867-1899 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Account book, 1877-1891 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Account book, 1936-1942 (Box 22a)
  - Account book, 1948-1953 (Box 22a)
  - Account book, 1953-1959 (Box 22b)
  - Account book, 1959-1965 (Box 22b)
  - Account book, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Accounts and receipts, Loose, 1867-1878 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Accounts and receipts, Loose, 1880-1882 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Accounts and receipts, Loose, 1894-1899 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Accounts and receipts, Loose, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Accounts and receipts, Loose, nd (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Act of Incorporation, 1811 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Admittance book, 1850-1875 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Admittance list, 1950-1963 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Admittance book, 1865-1927 (Box 23)
  - Admittance book, A-C, 1961-1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Admittance book, D-W 1961-1966 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Admittance list, Abstracted from books 1876-1935 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Application forms, blank (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Apprentice/indentures, c. 1829 and 1900 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Architectural plan, 1958, nd (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, Reports, 1877-1886 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors, Sympathy statements, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors, List, 1805-2006 (Box 24, Folder 8a)
  - Brochures, c. 1940-1960 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1956-1965 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1966-1970 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Cash receipt sheets, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Certificates, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Charters, 1874-1921 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1843-1849 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1915-1973 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1995-2005 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Constitution and By-laws, 1811-1898 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Constitution and By-laws, 1921-2001 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Contract, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Contracts, School Board of Richmond, 1967-1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Collins Denny III, 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Evaluations and References, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, General, 1867-1937 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, General, 1939-1946 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, General, 1948-1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Memorial Home and Childrens Clinic, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Resident parents, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Day Care Center, 1960-1969 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Day Care Center and Recreation Buildings, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Deeds, 1968-1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Employment applications, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Employee Pension Trust, 1962-1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Endowment, William Barret, 1890 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Endowment, Elizabeth W. Fry, 1895 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Endowment, Ann Hubbard, 1867 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Endowment, Fannie R. Pollard, 1949-1964 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Endowment, Mann S. Valentine c. 1890 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Endowment, Edmund Walls (includes copy of will), 1841 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Endowment and investments, Miscellaneous, 1962-1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Films, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Furber Silver Exhibit, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Edwin Gould Foundation for Children, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - History, A Brief History of the Memorial Foundation of Richmond, Virginia, 1805-1954, by Marymor Sanborn (Box 26)
  - History, Memorial Foundation for Children, 1805-1965 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - History, Memorial Foundation for Children, 1805-1965, Draft (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - History, Memorial Foundation for Children, 1805-2005 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - History, Notes, 1962-1971 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - History, Notes (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - History, Notes (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - History, Crippled Children's Hospital (Richmond, Virginia): The First Sixty Years, by Marjorie Branner Adams, 1979 (Box 27)
  - Hollywood Cemetery, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Inspection report, 1961 September (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Insurance policies, 1953-1969 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - List of Securities and Report of Trustees, 1900-1919 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Loan agreement, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Manual of Operation, c. 1950 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Guidance Clinic, 1944-1964 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Guidance Clinic, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Guidance Clinic Study, 1962-1969 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Mental Health in Virginia (Publication- Vol. 16, No. 3), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Milk Fund, 1963-1966 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, 1871 December- 1894 October (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1893-1899 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1894 December- 1907 December (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1916 June- 1918 February (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and resolutions, 1892-1923 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1915-1921 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and President's Reports, 1915-1936 (Box 28)